
The rules of the game
----------------------------

A human player competes against the computer. Both players throw 5 dice at the same time. The score of each throw for
 each player is the sum of the numbers shown on the faces of the dice. The objective of the game is to reach a score
 of 101 or more (instead of 101 another target can be set by the human before play starts) by throwing 5 dice as many
 times as necessary.

After a roll, each player may either score it or take up to two optional rerolls. For each reroll, he may reroll all
 of the dice or select any of the dice to keep and only reroll the remainder. He may score at any time, thus ending 
his current throw; after the second reroll (three rolls total) he must score it.

After both players score their rolls, the procedure is repeated until one of the players reach 101 or more points by 
summing all of their scores. If both players reach 101 or more with the same number of attempts (a single attempt is 
considered as one roll followed by 2 optional rerolls) the player with the highest score wins.

As an example, assume that the human player scores 30 points in the ﬁrst attempt (a roll followed by 2 optional rerolls),
 25 in the second, 11 in the third, 28 in the fourth and 15 in the ﬁfth achieving a total score of 109 in ﬁve attempts. 

If the computer did not score 101 in four attempts or more than 109 in ﬁve attempts, the human wins. In the case that 
both the computer and the human achieved the same score in the ﬁve attempts (i.e. 109 in the example), each player throws
 for a last time all ﬁve dice and the player with the highest sum in that roll wins (no optional rerolls are allowed in 
this case). In the case of a tie again, both players keep rethrowing all ﬁve dice until one of them wins!